sanebox.com 2011-03-22

# SaneBox: Get Through Email Faster

(Thank you [Better Business Bureau](http://www.bbbonline.org/privacy/sample_privacy.asp) for the bulk of this privacy policy.) 

This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. You accepted this policy when you signed up for our Service. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. Should a revision prove unacceptable to you, please contact us (see below). We last modified this policy on March 2, 2010\. 

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. It represents our good-faith efforts to ensure your privacy and provide you with a great service. 

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the SaneBox. The types of personal information collected include: 

  * Email address
  * For third party site-support (e.g., Google Mail) we may have to store authorization credentials and related information for other sites. We will make it clear that we are requesting this information before you provide it and you can contact to have it removed.
  * Data you give us permission to access (e.g., your Google Mail or Contacts)
  * Comments you make in our forums or elsewhere on our website

## The Way We Use Information

We use your email address to communicate with you and to authenticate with 3rd party products integrated with our system. We will never sell or rent your email address or ANY personally identifiable information to another company. 

For diagnostic purposes, our engineers may have access to private data (e.g., to fix a problem with the website). Before gaining such access, however, they must get management approval, and we are committed to maintaining the privacy of that data. Regardless, we will not read the bodies of your email messages (we may have to look at the envelopes (To/From/Subject/Date) as part of our diagnosis, but we ignore the bodies of messages). 

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies in order to track authentication and other session information. These cookies are not shared with other sites (unless we explicitly identify that information is being shared with another site). 

Of course, all personally identifiable information gathered can be disclosed to judicial or other government agencies subject to warrants, subpoenas or other governmental orders. But absent a legal compulsion, we have no plans to divulge your information. 

Finally, we do not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

All payments and payment information on our site is handled through [Spreedly.com](http://spreedly.com/info/faq/) which is fully PCI DSS compliant. [PCI DSS](https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/security_standards/pci_dss.shtml) is the global standard for safegaurding financial transaction data. No customer financial information is ever stored within our computer systems. 

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

## Who Owns Your Data?

You own the data associated with your account. And, at any time, you can securely remove your data from our servers by logging into your account and requesting such a deletion. This will be true even during a corporate merger or a corporate bankruptcy. 

We only access the envelope and header information associated with your emails. The actual bodies of your emails are never downloaded or accessed within our computer systems. 

When you cancel your membership, we not only securely delete all information on our servers associated with your mail account but we also delete any labels or flags we might have created - so not only will we no longer have any of your data on our servers, but also your email will look exactly like it did before you signed up with us 

If for any reason, Visible Certainty, Inc. decides to close SaneBox , all users will be contacted by email and their account information will be securely deleted from our servers in a timely manner. 

And remember that we will only backup meta data - never the actual envelopes so once securely deleted there is no possible place to recover them from. 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain via the website. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

## How To Contact Us

We can always be reached at:

Visible Certainty, Inc.  
211 Newbury Street, Unit #3  
Boston MA 02116

or by email at: [support@sanebox.com](mailto:support@sanebox.com)
